So I told Carl nobody, no matter how famous their parents are, nobody is allowed to climb
所以我告訴卡爾沒有人，無論他們的父母多有名，任何人都不被允許攀爬
on the dinosaur.
在恐龍身上。
But of course, this went right in one ear.
當然，這正好傳到了一隻耳朵裡。
I love how he cares so much about stuff.
我喜歡他如此關心事物。
If I squint, I can pretend he's Alan Alda.
如果我瞇起眼睛，我可以假裝他是艾倫·阿爾達。
Oh good, another dinosaur story.
哦，太好了，又一個恐龍故事。
One of those is going to become extinct.
其中之一即將滅絕。
If I was a superhero who could fly and be invisible, that would be the best.
如果我是一個能飛又能隱身的超級英雄那就最好了。
What does Rachel see in this guy?
雷切爾在這個人身上看到了什麼？
I love Rachel.
我愛雷切爾。
I wish she was my wife.
我希望她是我的妻子。
Who's singing?
誰在唱歌？
Hey, when you guys were kids and you played Happy Days, who were you?
嘿，當你們還是孩子的時候，你們玩快樂時光時，你們是誰？
I was always Richie.
我一直是裡奇。
I was always Joni.
我一直是喬尼。
Question, was Egg the Geller's the war cry of your neighborhood?
問題是，蓋勒埃格的口號是你家附近的戰爭口號嗎？
Ew, oh, it's the Mattress King.
呃，哦，這是床墊王。
Don't look, honey, change the channel, change the channel.
別看，親愛的，換頻道，換頻道。
Wait, wait.
等等，等等。
I want to see this.
我想看看這個。
After I divorce him, half of that kingdom is going to be mine.
等我跟他離婚之後，那個王國的一半就歸我了。
Despair fills the mattress showroom.
床墊陳列室裡充滿了絕望。
My kingdom is suddenly without a queen.
我的王國突然沒有女王了。
I'm so depressed.
我好鬱悶啊
I'm going to slash my prices.
我要削減我的價格。
Check it out.
一探究竟。
$4.99 for a pillow top queen set.
加墊大床套裝 4.99 美元。
I'm going medieval on prices.
我對價格的看法是中世紀的。
What a wank.
真是手淫啊。
Oh, I cannot believe he's using our divorce to sell mattresses.
哦，我不敢相信他利用我們的離婚來賣床墊。
I know.
我知道。
At $4.99 for a pillow top queen set, who cares about the divorce?
一套加墊大床套裝售價 4.99 美元，誰在乎離婚呢？
Those babies will sell themselves.
那些嬰兒會賣掉自己。
And I'm appalled for you, by the way.
順便說一句，我為你感到震驚。
I'm close, I'm cheap, I'm the king.
我很接近，我很便宜，我是國王。
He stuffs that codpiece, right?
他塞滿了密碼，對嗎？
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
Hey, here you go.
嘿，給你。
Oh, you know what?
哦，你知道嗎？
I asked for no cinnamon on top.
我要求上面不要加肉桂。
Oh.
哦。
Yeah, okay.
是啊，好吧。
All right, Daddy, we'll see you tomorrow night.
好吧，爸爸，我們明天晚上見。
Okay, bye.
好的，再見。
We?
我們？
Are having dinner with my dad tomorrow night.
明天晚上和我爸爸一起吃晚餐。
I hope that's okay.
我希望沒關係。
Oh, shoot.
哦，射擊。
Tomorrow's not so good.
明天不太好。
I'm supposed to fall off the Empire State Building and land on a bicycle with no seat, so.
我應該從帝國大廈掉下來，然後騎在沒有座位的腳踏車上，所以。
Ross, my father doesn't hate you.
羅斯，我父親並不恨你。
Please, he refers to me as wet head.
拜託，他稱我為濕頭。
Come on, honey, he calls everybody by a nickname.
來吧，親愛的，他用暱稱稱呼每個人。
Okay, look, just one dinner, please.
好吧，聽著，請吃一頓晚餐。
One night for me, please.
請給我住一晚。
I just want him to love you like I do.
我只是想讓他像我一樣愛你。
All right, well, not exactly like I do, but.
好吧，好吧，不完全像我一樣，但是。
But if you do come to dinner, I'll love you like I do and that black thing that you like.
但如果你真的來吃晚飯，我會像以前一樣愛你和你喜歡的那個黑色的東西。
I'll go.
我去吧。
Fine.
美好的。
Thank you.
謝謝。
Hi, Gunther.
嗨，岡瑟。
Yeah, we'll see.
是的，我們拭目以待。
Hey, you guys.
嘿，你們。
Guess what?
你猜怎麼著？
I got a gig.
我得到了一份演出。
See, that's why I can never be an actor, because I can't say gig.
看，這就是為什麼我永遠不能成為一名演員，因為我不能說“演出”。
Yeah, I can't say croissant.
是的，我不能說牛角麵包。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
What's the part?
那是什麼部分？
Oh, it's not a part, no.
哦，這不是一部分，不是。
I'm teaching acting for soap operas down at the Learning Extension.
我在學習拓展中心教肥皂剧表演。
Come on, that's great.
來吧，那太好了。
Yeah, yeah, it's like, it's like my chance to give something back to the acting community.
是的，是的，這就像我有機會回饋演藝界。
You know, you're probably not allowed to sleep with any of your students.
你知道，你可能不被允許和你的任何學生睡覺。
I know.
我知道。
Ugh, I don't know, Monica.
呃，我不知道，莫妮卡。
It feels funny just being here.
光是待在這裡就覺得很有趣。
I mean, if you buy a bed from Janice's ex-husband, that's like betraying Chandler.
我的意思是，如果你從珍妮絲的前夫那裡買一張床，那就等於背叛了錢德勒。
Not at these prices.
不是按照這些價格。
Hi.
你好。
You know, in England, you don't have to buy a bed.
你知道，在英國，你不必買床。
This car would be on the other side of the store.
這輛車將在商店的另一邊。
Whoosh.
嗖嗖。
Oh.
哦。
Phoebe, come here.
菲比，過來。
Oh, this is my new bed.
哦，這是我的新床。
You gotta feel this bad boy.
你一定要感受一下這個壞男孩。
Ugh, Monica, it still feels so weird, you know?
呃，莫妮卡，還是覺得很奇怪，你知道嗎？
Chandler's your friend.
錢德勒是你的朋友。
Oh.
哦。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Ugh.
啊。
All right, take this bed.
好吧，就這張床吧。
You can make other friends.
你可以結交其他朋友。
Good evening.
晚上好。
I am Mr. Tribbiani.
我是特里比亞尼先生。
And I'll be teaching acting for soap operas.
我將教授肥皂剧表演。
Unfortunately, tonight will be my only class because
不幸的是，今晚將是我唯一的課，因為
due to a rare blood disease, I only have two weeks to live.
由於一種罕見的血液疾病，我只剩下兩週的生命了。
So, do we get our deposit back?
那我們的押金能拿回來嗎？
I'm supposed to be an example of acting for soap operas.
我應該成為肥皂剧表演的榜樣。
Then why are you only teaching tonight?
那你為什麼只在今晚教課？
I'm not.
我不是。
Look, why don't we get straight to the lesson, okay?
聽著，我們為什麼不直接上課，好嗎？
All right.
好的。
Now, um, on my first day as Dr. Drake Remore on Days of Our Lives,
現在，嗯，在我在《我們的日子》中飾演 Drake Remore 博士的第一天，
uh, I learned that one of the most important things
呃，我瞭解到最重要的事情之一
in soap opera acting is re-acting.
在肥皂剧中，表演就是重新表演。
This does not mean acting again.
這並不意味著再次行動。
It means you don't have a line, but someone else just did.
這意味著您沒有排隊，但其他人已經排隊了。
And it goes something like this.
事情是這樣的。
Thanks. Thanks. Thanks a lot.
謝謝。謝謝。多謝。
Oh, by the way, before I forget,
哦，順便說一下，在我忘記之前，
to work in soap operas,
從事肥皂剧工作，
some of you are gonna have to become much more attractive.
你們中的一些人必須變得更加有吸引力。
All right. Moving right along.
好的。向右移動。
Hi.
你好。
Hey.
嘿。
Oh, how was teaching last night?
哦，昨晚的教學怎麼樣？
Oh, it was great.
哦，太棒了。
Yeah, you get to say stuff like,
是的，你可以說這樣的話，
hey, the bell doesn't dismiss you.
嘿，鈴聲不會解僱你。
I dismiss you.
我解僱了你。
Oh, nice.
哦，不錯。
Oh, and guess what?
哦，你猜怎麼著？
I got an audition for All My Children.
我參加了《我所有的孩子》的試鏡。
Oh, yay!
哦，耶！
Yeah, it's this great part, this boxer named Nick,
是的，這是一個偉大的部分，這個名叫尼克的拳擊手，
and I'm so, so right for it, you know?
我非常非常適合，你知道嗎？
He's just like me.
他就像我一樣。
Except, like, he's a boxer and has an evil twin.
只不過，他是一名拳擊手，並且有一個邪惡的雙胞胎。
Oh.
哦。
Dum-da-da-dum.
咚咚咚。
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿。
Delivery from the mattress cave.
從床墊洞穴運送。
You, Miss Geller?
你，蓋勒小姐？
Okay.
好的。
Sign here.
在這裡簽名。
Ooh, do I have a middle name?
哦，我有中間名嗎？
All right, Monica Falula...
好吧，莫妮卡·法魯拉…
Geller.
蓋勒。
It's that bedroom there.
就是那間臥室。
Thank you.
謝謝。
Hey, Monica bought a bed from the Mattress King?
嘿，莫妮卡從床墊王那裡買了一張床？
Yeah.
是的。
So please, please, please don't say anything to Chandler.
所以拜託拜託拜託不要對錢德勒說任何話。
You want me to lie to Chandler?
你想讓我對錢德勒撒謊嗎？
Is that a problem?
這是一個問題嗎？
No.
不。
Oh, hey, hey, Nick the boxer.
哦，嘿，嘿，拳擊手尼克。
Let's see what you got.
讓我們看看你得到了什麼。
All right, yeah, put them up.
好吧，是的，把它們放上來。
Come on.
快點。
Hey, you're, uh, you're pretty good at this.
嘿，你，呃，你在這方面很擅長。
Yeah, well, I had to learn.
是的，好吧，我必須學習。
I was staying at the Y,
我住在Y，
and some of the young men weren't acting Christian enough.
有些年輕人表現得不夠基督徒。
Oh.
哦。
Hey, now.
嘿，現在。
Hey!
嘿！
Ow!
噢！
And I'm bleeding.
我在流血。
Oh, oh!
哦，哦！
Okay, great.
好的，太好了。
Wow, and I'm a vegetarian.
哇，我是素食主義者。
All right, all right, I'm sorry.
好吧好吧，對不起。
We'll put some ice on it.
我們會在上面放一些冰。
Okay.
好的。
Put your head back.
把頭向後仰。
All right.
好的。
I can't see.
我看不到。
All right, I'll have you.
好吧，我會擁有你的。
Oh, God.
哦，上帝。
Which bedroom do you want it in, Miss Geller?
蓋勒小姐，你想把它放在哪間臥室？
Oh, um, it's the compulsively neat one by the window, okay?
哦，嗯，就是靠窗的那個，太整潔了，好嗎？
Yeah, sure.
是的，當然。
Hi, Daddy.
嗨，爸爸。
This is where they put us?
這就是他們把我們安置在哪裡？
What, there was no table available in the kitchen?
什麼，廚房裡沒有桌子？
Hello, baby.
你好，寶貝。
You remember Ross?
你還記得羅斯嗎？
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
Nice to see you again, Dr. Green.
很高興再次見到你，格林博士。
So...
所以...
How's the library?
圖書館怎麼樣？
Uh, museum.
呃，博物館。
What happened to the library?
圖書館怎麼了？
There never was a library.
從來沒有圖書館。
I mean, there are libraries.
我的意思是，有圖書館。
It's just that I, um, I've never worked at one.
只是我，嗯，我從來沒有工作過。
You know what's really good here?
你知道這裡有什麼真正的好處嗎？
The lobster.
龍蝦。
Mmm.
嗯。
What do you say?
你怎麼說？
Shall I just order three?
Yeah, if you're really hungry.
是的，如果你真的餓了。
It was a joke.
這是一個笑話。
I made a joke.
我開了個玩笑。
Yeah, actually, Daddy, Ross is allergic to lobster.
是的，事實上，爸爸，羅斯對龍蝦過敏。
What kind of person is allergic to lobster?
什麼樣的人對龍蝦過敏？
I guess the kind of person that works in a library.
我猜是那種在圖書館工作的人。
It's not a library.
這不是圖書館。
I know, it's a museum.
我知道，這是一座博物館。
Well, you're the only one around here who can make a joke.
好吧，你是這裡唯一會開玩笑的人。
At least mine was funny.
至少我的很有趣。
Uh, waiter.
呃，服務生。
We will have two lobsters and a menu.
我們要兩隻龍蝦和一份選單。
So, Dr. Green, how's the old boat?
那麼，格林博士，那艘舊船怎麼樣了呢？
They found rust.
他們發現了鐵鏽。
You know what rust does to a boat?
你知道生鏽對船有什麼影響嗎？
Gives it a nice antique-y look?
給它一個漂亮的古董外觀嗎？
Rust is boat cancer, Ross.
羅斯，銹病是船癌。
Wow, I'm sorry.
哇，對不起。
When I was a kid, I lost a bike to that.
當我還是個孩子的時候，我就因此失去了一輛腳踏車。
Excuse me for a moment.
請原諒我一下。
Will you please?
請你好嗎？
I want to say goodnight to the Levines before we go.
在我們離開之前我想向萊文夫婦道晚安。
Okay.
好的。
Honey, stop.
親愛的，停下來。
It's not that bad.
沒那麼糟。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh.
哦。
Uh-oh.
呃哦。
I think your dad must have added wrong.
我想你爸爸肯定加錯了。
He only tipped, like, four percent.
他只給了百分之四的小費。
Yeah.
是的。
That's Daddy.
那是爸爸。
That's Daddy?
那是爸爸？
What, doesn't it bother you?
什麼，這不困擾你嗎？
You're a waitress.
你是一名女服務生。
Yes, it bothers me, Ross.
是的，這讓我很困擾，羅斯。
But, you know, if he was a regular at the coffee house,
但是，你知道，如果他是咖啡館的常客，
I'd be serving him sneezers.
我會給他打噴嚏。
So?
所以？
So, Ross, I bugged him about this a million times.
所以，羅斯，我為此騷擾了他一百萬次。
He's not going to change.
他不會改變。
Do you really serve people sneezers?
你真的為人們提供打噴嚏服務嗎？
Well, um, I don't.
嗯，嗯，我不知道。
All right, kids, ready?
好了，孩子們，準備好了嗎？
Yes.
是的。
Thanks again, Dr. Green.
再次感謝，格林博士。
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
噢，等等，等等，等等，等等。
I think I forgot my receipt.
我想我忘記了收據。
Oh, no, you don't need that.
哦，不，你不需要那個。
Why not?
為什麼不呢？
The carbon, it's messy.
碳，很亂。
I mean, it gets on your fingers and causes the,
我的意思是，它沾到你的手指會導致，
the, uh, night blindness.
呃，夜盲症。
What is this?
這是什麼？
Who put a 20 down there?
誰在那裡放了20？
Huh?
啊？
Oh, yeah, that would be me.
哦，是的，那就是我。
Um, I have, I have a problem.
嗯，我有，我有一個問題。
I, I tip way too much.
我，我給的小費太多了。
Way, way too much.
方式，太多了。
It's a sickness, really.
這確實是一種病。
Yeah, it is.
是的，確實如此。
It is.
這是。
We really, really have to do something about it.
我們真的、真的必須為此做些什麼。
Oh, no.
哦，不。
Excuse me.
打擾一下。
You think I'm cheap?
你覺得我佔便宜嗎？
Oh, Dad, you know, he didn't mean anything by that.
哦，爸爸，你知道，他這麼說並沒有什麼意思。
He really didn't.
他確實沒有。
Nothing I do means anything, really.
我所做的一切都沒有任何意義，真的。
This is nice.
這很好。
I pay $200 for dinner, you put down 20,
我付了200美元的晚餐，你付了20美元，
and you come out looking like Mr. Bigshot.
你出來的時候看起來就像大人物先生。
You really want to be Mr. Bigshot?
你真的想成為大人物先生嗎？
Oh.
哦。
Here, I'll tell you what.
在這裡，我會告訴你什麼。
You pay the whole bill, Mr. Bigshot, all right?
大人物先生，你付全部帳單，好嗎？
Well, Mr. Bigshot is better than wet head.
好吧，大人物先生比濕漉漉的腦袋好。
Okay, some tricks of the trade.
好吧，一些交易技巧。
Now, I've never been able to cry as an actor,
現在，身為演員我從來沒有哭過，
so if I'm in a scene where I have to cry,
所以如果我在一個不得不哭的場景中
I cut a hole in my pocket,
我在口袋裡割了一個洞
take a pair of tweezers,
拿一把鑷子，
and just start pulling.
然後開始拉。
Okay?
好的？
Or, uh, or let's say I want to convey
或者，呃，或者說我想傳達
that I've, uh, just done something evil.
我，呃，剛剛做了一些邪惡的事情。
Well, that would be your basic,
嗯，這就是你的基本，
I've got a fishhook in my eyebrow and I like it.
我眉毛上有一個魚鉤，我喜歡它。
Yeah? Okay.
是的？好的。
Let's say I've just gotten bad news.
假設我剛剛得到壞訊息。
Well, all I do there is try and divide 232 by 13.
好吧，我所做的就是嘗試將 232 除以 13。
And that's how it's done.
事情就是這樣完成的。
Great soap opera acting tonight, everybody.
今晚肥皂剧表演很棒，大家。
Class dismissed.
下課了。
Hey, Mr. Trim.
嘿，特里姆先生。
Hey.
嘿。
Guess what?
你猜怎麼著？
I got an audition.
我參加了試鏡。
Oh?
哦？
One of my students got an audition.
我的一位學生參加了試鏡。
I'm so proud.
我很自豪。
I was wondering if you would consider coaching me for it.
我想知道你是否會考慮指導我。
You bet.
你打賭。
What's the part?
那是什麼部分？
Oh, it's great.
哦，太棒了。
It's a role in All My Children, Nick the Boxer.
這是《我的孩子們》中的一個角色，拳擊手尼克。
You had to do it, didn't you?
你必須這麼做，不是嗎？
You couldn't just leave it alone.
你不能就這樣不管它。
Four percent, okay?
百分之四，可以嗎？
I tip more than that when there's a bug in my food.
當我的食物裡有蟲時，我給的小費會比這個多。
Ross, tonight was about the two of you getting along.
羅斯，今晚是你們兩個相處的日子。
Ugh.
啊。
Ugh, would you just see my chiropractor already?
呃，你能見見我的脊椎按摩師嗎？
Yeah, I'm going to go to a doctor
是的，我要去看醫生
who went to medical school at a mini mall.
誰在迷你商場上過醫學院。
Hey, Pheebs.
嘿，菲比斯。
What are you doing?
你在幹什麼？
I'm freaking out!
我嚇壞了！
Monica kind of trusted me with something
莫妮卡在某件事上信任了我
and she shouldn't have.
她不應該這樣做。
All right, I haven't lived here in a while,
好吧，我有一段時間沒在這裡住了，
so I have to ask you something.
所以我得問你一件事。
Does Monica still turn the lights on in her bedroom?
莫妮卡還開著臥室的燈嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
I am so dead.
我就這麼死了。
All right, look, here's the bottom line, Ross.
好吧，看，這就是底線，羅斯。
This is fixable if we act fast, okay?
如果我們行動迅速，這個問題是可以解決的，好嗎？
So I'll invite him to brunch tomorrow
所以明天我會邀請他吃早午餐
and you can make nice.
你可以和善。
Honey, I have tried to make nice.
親愛的，我已經盡力表現得友善了。
It doesn't work.
這不起作用。
Okay, look, Ross, I realize that my father is difficult,
好吧，聽著，羅斯，我意識到我父親很難相處，
but that's why you have got to be the bigger man here.
但這就是為什麼你必須成為這裡的大人物。
Look, sweetie, I could be the bigger man.
聽著，親愛的，我可以成為更大的人。
I could be the biggest man.
我可以成為最大的男人。
I could be a big, huge, giant man
我可以成為一個高大、巨大、巨人的男人
and it still wouldn't make any difference,
但這仍然沒有任何區別
except that I could pick your father up
除了我可以去接你父親
and say, like me, like me, tiny doctor!
並說，像我一樣，像我一樣，小醫生！
Okay, well, can't you just try it one more time, Ross?
好吧，羅斯，你就不能再試一次嗎？
For me, for me.
為了我，為了我。
Rachel, one brunch is not going to solve anything.
雷切爾，一頓早午餐解決不了任何問題。
You've got to face it, okay?
你必須面對它，好嗎？
We're never going to get along.
我們永遠合不來。
Okay, well, you are just going to have to, okay?
好吧，好吧，你必須這樣做，好嗎？
Because I've already got a mother and a father
因為我已經有爸爸媽媽了
who cannot stay in the same room together, okay?
誰不能一起待在同一個房間，好嗎？
I don't want to have to have a separate room for you, too.
我也不想給你一個單獨的房間。
Okay, okay, okay.
好吧，好吧，好吧。
I'll get the bagels.
我去拿百吉餅。
What's this?
這是什麼？
Isn't it cool?
是不是很酷？
Vroom, vroom!
嗚嗚嗚！
This is not the bed I ordered.
這不是我訂購的床。
I know!
我知道！
You must have won, like, a contest or something.
你一定是贏了比賽之類的勝利。
Vroom!
弗魯姆！
Phoebe!
菲比！
Why is this car in my bedroom?
這輛車為什麼在我的臥室？
I'm sorry, okay?
對不起，好嗎？
I wasn't looking,
我沒有看，
and the store said that they won't take it back
而且店家說不會退貨
because you've signed for it.
因為你已經簽收了。
When did I sign for it?
我什麼時候簽的？
When I was you!
當我是你的時候！
You know what?
你知道嗎？
It's all Joey's fault,
都是喬伊的錯
because he left his nose open.
因為他把鼻子開啟了。
Did you make brownies today?
今天你做了布朗尼蛋糕嗎？
Knock, knock.
敲，敲。
Quick, take off your dress.
快點，脫掉你的衣服。
You won't notice the bed.
你不會注意到那張床。
Hey, I'm going for sushi.
嘿，我去吃壽司。
Does anybody want, uh...
有人想要嗎，呃...
Whoa, somebody missed the off-ramp.
哇，有人錯過了出口匝道。
It's Monica's bed.
這是莫妮卡的床。
What?
什麼？
Okay.
好的。
It's a race car.
這是一輛賽車。
So this has always been
所以一直都是這樣
Monica's bed.
莫妮卡的床。
Okay, well, you're just noticing now?
好吧，你現在才注意到？
How self-involved are you?
你的自我參與程度如何？
Okay, well,
好吧，好吧，
if this bed isn't new,
如果這張床不是新的
then how come there's plastic on the mattress?
那麼床墊上怎麼會有塑膠呢？
Sometimes I have bad dreams.
有時我會做惡夢。
Look, I just saw
你看，我剛剛看到
my best friend's brain
我最好朋友的大腦
smeared across the canvas.
塗抹在畫布上。
It's not gonna be me.
這不會是我。
Not me.
不是我。
Wow.
哇。
That was good.
那很好。
That was...
那是...
Tweezers?
鑷子？
No.
不。
It was really good.
真的很好。
Thanks.
謝謝。
Any suggestions?
有什麼建議嗎？
Hmm, I...
嗯，我...
You told him to play the boxer gay?
你讓他扮演同性戀拳擊手？
Well, I might have said
好吧，我可能會說
super gay.
超級同性戀。
Joey, the last time an actor did something this bad,
喬伊，上次有演員做這麼糟糕的事
a president died.
一位總統去世了。
Lincoln...
林肯...
Booth...
展位...
Something happened at the tunnel?
隧道裡發生什麼事了？
Joey, you're this guy's teacher.
喬伊，你是這傢伙的老師。
I mean, how could you do this?
我的意思是，你怎麼能這樣做？
Because, Monica, the guy's so good,
因為，莫妮卡，這傢伙太棒了，
and I really, really want this part.
我真的非常想要這個部分。
Well, if you really, really want it,
好吧，如果你真的真的想要的話，
then it's okay.
那就沒關係了。
Hi, Daddy.
嗨，爸爸。
Baby.
嬰兒。
Ross?
羅斯？
Dr. Green, how are you?
格林博士，你好嗎？
Thanks for dinner last night.
謝謝昨晚的晚餐。
Thank you for teaching me
謝謝你教我
a valuable lesson.
寶貴的一課。
Nice hair.
頭髮不錯。
What'd you do, swim here?
在這裡游泳做什麼？
Okay, that's it.
好吧，就是這樣。
I can't take it anymore.
我再也受不了了。
What? What? He's interested in you.
什麼？什麼？他對你感興趣。
He likes your hair, and he just wants to know how you got here.
他喜歡你的頭髮，他只是想知道你是怎麼來到這裡的。
Oh, please.
哦，拜託。
Sweetie, it's hopeless, okay? I'm just gonna go.
親愛的，這是沒有希望的，好嗎？我要走了。
What? Ross.
什麼？羅斯.
Look, I'm sorry. It's just...
聽著，我很抱歉。這只是...
Ross? What's with the neck?
羅斯？脖子怎麼了？
He's got this thing, and I keep telling him to go to my chiropractor.
他得了這個病，我一直叫他去看我的脊椎按摩師。
You're still going to that chiropractor?
你還要去那個脊椎按摩師那裡嗎？
That man couldn't get into med school in Ixtapa.
那個人無法進入伊斯塔帕的醫學院。
Thank you. That's what I keep saying.
謝謝。這就是我一直說的話。
Excuse me.
打擾一下。
Dr. Bobby happens to be an excellent doctor.
鮑比醫生恰好是一位出色的醫生。
Oh, wait a minute. His name is Dr. Bobby?
哦，等一下。他的名字叫鮑比博士？
Well, that's his last name.
嗯，這是他的姓氏。
And his first name.
還有他的名字。
He's Bobby Bobby?
他是鮑比鮑比？
Ahem.
咳咳。
It's Robert Bobby.
這是羅伯特·鮑比。
Oh.
哦。
And, um, excuse me, he helps me.
而且，嗯，對不起，他幫了我。
Oh, please. Ask her how.
哦，拜託。問她怎麼辦。
What do you need help for?
你需要什麼幫助？
With my alignment. I got one leg shorter than the other.
與我的對齊。我的一條腿比另一條腿短。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Argue with that.
與此爭論。
What? It's true. My right leg is two inches shorter.
什麼？這是真的。我的右腿短了兩吋。
Come on, you're just tilting.
來吧，你只是傾斜了。
Alexa, fine.
亞歷克斯，好吧。
I know that.
我知道。
So what are you letting her go to a chiropractor for?
那你讓她去看脊椎按摩師做什麼？
I'm sorry. Let her?
對不起。讓她？
What can I do? She doesn't listen to me about renter's insurance, either.
我能做些什麼？她也不聽我關於房客保險的事。
Wait a minute. You don't have renter's insurance?
等一下。你沒有租客保險嗎？
No.
不。
But what if somebody steals something?
但如果有人偷東西怎麼辦？
How are you going to run after them
你要怎麼追他們
with one leg shorter than the other?
一條腿比另一條腿短？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Hey, would you, uh, would you like some juice?
嘿，你想，呃，想喝點果汁嗎？
I'd love some juice.
我想要一些果汁。
Okay.
好的。
Wow, this is going so well.
哇，一切進展順利。
Did you see us? Did you see?
你看到我們了嗎？你有沒有看到？
Yeah, honey, I'm standing right there.
是的，親愛的，我就站在那裡。
Why don't you just tell them about the mall?
為什麼不告訴他們商場的事呢？
I haven't gotten checked yet.
我還沒有被檢查過。
Excellent.
出色的。
There will come a time in each of your careers
每個人的職業生涯都會有這樣的時刻
when you'll have a chance to screw over
當你有機會搞砸的時候
another soap opera actor.
另一位肥皂剧演員。
I had such an opportunity
我有這樣的機會
in the recent present.
在最近的現在。
And I'm ashamed to say
我很羞愧地說
that I took it.
我拿走了它。
I advised a fellow actor
我建議一位演員
to play a role
發揮作用
homosexually.
同性戀。
Yeah.
是的。
We both auditioned for the part,
我們都參加了這個角色的試鏡
and, uh,
還有，呃，
as it turned out,
事實證明，
they, uh,
他們，呃，
they liked the stupid gay thing
他們喜歡愚蠢的同性戀事物
and cast him.
並施放他。
Now
現在
he's got a two-year contract
他有一份為期兩年的合約
opposite
對面
Susan Lucci,
蘇珊·盧奇,
the first lady
第一夫人
of daytime television.
的日間電視節目。
And me?
而我呢？
Me, I'm stuck here
我，我被困在這裡了
teaching a bunch of people
教導一群人
most of whom are too ugly
大多數都太醜了
to even be on TV.
甚至上電視。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
對不起。對不起。
Thank you.
謝謝。
Uh, may I help you?
呃，我可以幫你嗎？
Yes, hi. I talked to you on the phone.
是的，嗨。我在電話裡和你談過。
I'm the lady who got stuck with the race car bed.
我就是那個被賽車床困住的女士。
Look, it's like I told you
聽著，就像我告訴過你的一樣
there's nothing I can do.
我無能為力。
You signed for it.
你簽了字。
Monica Falula Geller.
莫妮卡·法盧拉·蓋勒。
All right, Jester, man.
好吧，小丑，夥計。
Look, we want to see the king.
聽著，我們想見國王。
Nobody sees the king.
沒有人看到國王。
Okay, I'm talking
好吧，我正在說話
to the king.
給國王。
Hey, you can't go back there.
嘿，你不能再回到那裡了。
Oh...
哦...
my...
我的...
God.
上帝。
Vroom!
弗魯姆！
Hey, watch it, lady!
嘿，注意點，女士！
Vroom!
弗魯姆！
Hey, hey, good looking.
嘿嘿嘿，好帥啊
Vroom!
弗魯姆！
All right, I'll leave.
好吧，我這就走。
My bed's so boring.
我的床太無聊了